<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>MyBetterWeb.site</title>
        <description>We build seo-optimized and mobile-friendly websites designed to perform across all devices. Generate leads or sales from customers on desktop computers or their phones.</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000//feed.xml" rel="self"
        type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:08:11 +0545</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:08:11 +0545</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
        
        <item>
            <title>Search Engine Optimization</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“MyBetterWeb is a cutting edge company that really “gets it”. Attentive, friendly, and knowledgeable staff. As a client for past few months, I can say with complete confidence that they are going to work very hard for you. The results speak for themselves and our company is quite impressed with the work they have done.” -&lt;a href=&quot;https://ultranet.netlify.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt; ultranet.com.np&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Proven Techniques&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Transparent Detailed Monthly Reports&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Certified Google Partner Team&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Technical Capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SEO services with proven results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;proven-ecommerce-seo-strategies&quot;&gt;Proven eCommerce SEO strategies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We create monthly reports that include all of your website’s key metrics (conversions, sales, traffic, rankings) and summarize exactly what work was performed on your website. After analyzing our results and progress, we’ll setup a call to discuss your monthly report and review our plans for the following month. This monthly process allows us to evaluate the effectiveness of our strategy in real-time and channel more energy into strategies that have a proven, direct impact on your bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;expert-seo-team-with-google-certification&quot;&gt;Expert SEO team with Google certification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketing your website through search engine optimization (SEO) is just as important as the way your website looks and functions. SEO can have a major positive impact on your visibility and it’s important to choose a professional search marketing agency that understands search engine algorithms and is experienced in providing tangible results. We’ve helped companies increase traffic by over 500% in less than 6 months and grow sales by hundred of thousands of dollars. Our search engine optimization services (SEO), will help display your website toward the top of organic search results for the keywords most important to your specific business&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 17:57:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/10/01/search-engine-optimization.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/10/01/search-engine-optimization.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>eCommerce Online Shop</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“We were looking for a company we could build a relationship with. We’ve dealt with a lot of people working out of their basement, and we needed to take it to the next level. Communication is excellent and they do what they say they are going to do.” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://usoft.store&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;usoft.store&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ecommerce-website-design-that-takes-your-business-to-the-next-level&quot;&gt;eCommerce website design that takes your business to the next level&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve worked on many eCommerce projects and know what it takes to generate sales. Utilizing responsive web design, your eCommerce website will be optimized for desktop, mobile and tablet shopping. With platform features like unlimited products and categories, to a secure one-page checkout, we make online shopping easy for customers to buy online and easy to manage for website owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;custom-ecommerce-functionality-to-streamline-your-business&quot;&gt;Custom eCommerce functionality to streamline your business&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From selling a product or subscription, to taking payments for a service, our team can develop the custom eCommerce website solution that’s perfect for your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-ecommerce-website-features-you-need-to-succeed&quot;&gt;The eCommerce website features you need to succeed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having a robust eCommerce website is the foundation of your online retail business, and we understand the importance of utilizing the latest technology to increase your profitability. Our eCommerce solutions offer the best in standard features and functionality while remaining completely customizable:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drive Sales Across All Devices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a desktop, tablet and mobile responsive eCommerce website, you’ll be able to increase your conversion rate and online purchases to grow your bottom line across all devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Homepage to Checkout, Fast!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developed using the latest technology and standards, you’ll have a blazing fast website that allows customers to go from browsing to checkout in seconds!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robust Product Features &amp;amp; Capabilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you have basic products or need product customization, unique product options or a whole set of custom product functionality, we’ve got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easily Manage Your Content &amp;amp; Scale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through a well-designed content management system (CMS), you can easily update pages, categories, products, articles, posts, banners and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Powerful Marketing Suite&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From advanced search engine optimization tools to running promotions, our sites are built to give you a suite of powerful marketing tools. Run BOGOs, create landing pages and drive revenue to your eCommerce website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 17:57:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/09/10/ecommerce-online-shop.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/09/10/ecommerce-online-shop.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Responsive Website</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“I love my website! It’s beautiful, professional, and easy to navigate. MyBetterWeb was a great company to work with. As a business owner, I definitely appreciate their great customer service, projects done in an efficient and timely manner, and a final product that exceeded my expectations and also made us won &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mwa.my/2017/may/khimyan-curry-a-malaysian-born-curry-paste&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Malaysia Website Awards 2017&lt;/a&gt;.” -&lt;a href=&quot;https://khimyan.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;khimyan.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Perform On All Devices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Manage One Code Base&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rank Higher&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy Mobile Checkout&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile Optimized Speeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;professional-web-design-and-ecommerce-website-design&quot;&gt;Professional web design and eCommerce website design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your website is the core anchor for your digital business and marketing efforts. Having a great website user experience requires understanding the problems different visitors have to solve. And there is a difference between responsive design and a completely separate mobile website. Both can be beneficial at times. If you want the same content on your mobile website as on your desktop of your website, responsive design is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rank-higher-in-mobile-search-results&quot;&gt;Rank higher in mobile search results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, if you’re looking for a mobile version that is extremely limited or a stripped down version of your full website, a separate mobile version may be a better option. The advantage to responsive design is that it allows the website to use the same code and same files for all displays, while a true mobile version is a separate code base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;best-user-experience-for-increased-online-revenue&quot;&gt;Best user experience for increased online revenue&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As mobile and tablet traffic continues to grow at a rapid pace, the need to have a site optimized for these devices is a necessity. Whether you have an informational website or an eCommerce website, responsive design allows for your customers to easily view, navigate and ultimately purchase from your business online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;app-like-website-feel--functionality&quot;&gt;App-like website feel &amp;amp; functionality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With responsive design the need for a separate mobile site and tablet optimized website is eliminated and your website will automatically “adapt” to the device it is being viewed on. You’ll end up with a site that looks great on a mobile device, tablet, desktop computer and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:57:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/08/13/responsive-website.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/08/13/responsive-website.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Business Website</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“The overall design and functionality far exceeds my expectations. Your dedication, constant engagement, and responsiveness made the process easy. You really went above and beyond! I’m already looking forward to having you build my next site.” -&lt;a href=&quot;https://thapa.coffee&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt; thapa.coffee&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;complete-custom-design-and-creative&quot;&gt;Complete custom design and creative&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With MyBetterWeb each corporate website is custom designed and developed to meet the needs and goals of your business. Our mission is to provide your corporation with a professional, branded website that’ll set your business apart from your competitors. Ease of navigation and calls to action are always in the forefront of our design process and websites that produce results are what MyBetterWeb is all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;easy-to-use-content-management-system&quot;&gt;Easy-to-use content management system&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corporate website design and eCommerce capabilities often work hand-in-hand, whether your website sells directly to the consumer or to distributors on a wholesale level. Every website developed offers you, the client, the ability to manage and maintain dealers and website content through an easy-to-use content management system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dominate Desktop &amp;amp; Mobile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bring your brands image to all devices. Our solutions perform on mobile, tablet and desktop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Code &amp;amp; Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Utilizing the latest in development standards, security, and hosting, your data will always be safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;eCommerce &amp;amp; Catalog Functionality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allow customers to purchase products or display items in catalog mode. Learn more about our Learn more on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://mybetterweb.site/#/2018/09/10/ecommerce-online-shop&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;eCommerce web design services page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning Fast Speeds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using the latest technology, we’ll optimize images and code to load quickly for mobile users.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 17:57:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/07/01/business-website.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/07/01/business-website.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Conversion Rate Optimization</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“Our web site was done very professionally. We like the layout and the time frame was great. Also, the price was very reasonable. Thanks for all your time and effort you put into this. We probably wouldn’t have a website even now if we didn’t find out about you.” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://shishutours.fun&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;shishutours.fun&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-the-most-of-your-website&quot;&gt;Make the most of your website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your conversion rate is very possibly the most important website statistic. The website conversion rate is the number that affects your bottom line and drives the growth of your business. MyBetterWeb specializes in turning your eCommerce website visitors into customers via our website conversion rate optimization service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;optimize-the-user-experience-and-call-to-action&quot;&gt;Optimize the user experience and call to action&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through our team’s expertise and analytical testing, we determine what changes your website needs in order to perform above and beyond industry standards. Whether you have an eCommerce website and are selling products online, or you’re a service based business looking to increase leads, we’ve worked with clients who have faced the same scenarios that you’re facing now. With ever-growing competition in the online space, it’s important to stay on top of your game and have a company dedicated to your ongoing success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;seo--conversion-rate-optimization-effects&quot;&gt;SEO &amp;amp; conversion rate optimization effects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understanding the connection between SEO and conversion rate is critical in any conversion optimization campaign. When searching on the web users are more likely to click and convert on results at the top. Typically, web users that go to the bottom of page 1 or to page 2, are merely “window shopping” and are not serious buyers. This connection drives down conversion rates and leads to worthless traffic. At MyBetterWeb our goal is to combine conversion rate optimization with SEO efforts to create a campaign that ranks, converts and sells your business better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-is-conversion-rate-optimization-works&quot;&gt;How is conversion rate optimization works?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Website audit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conversion rate optimization process is similar to a search engine optimization experience. We start by having MyBetterWeb team members review your website and put together “red flag” items. These are issues that we understand to be major issues from the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Filter data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we realize these and review them with the client, we fix the issues and move into an analytical phase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Analysis site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analytics allow us to determine traffic and visitor patterns on your website. Typical questions we ask are, “Where are visitors leaving?”, “Why are they not checking out?” and “How can we be sure they call you?”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Fine tuning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By looking at statistics we can figure out where weak spots are in your website and begin to implement improvements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Optimize further&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an ongoing process of making changes, analyzing the results and continuing to increase the conversion rate month after month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 17:57:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/06/01/conversion-rate-optimization.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/06/01/conversion-rate-optimization.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Paid Search Marketing</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;“MyBetterWeb helped us set up the campaign, build highly converting landing pages and they manage our campaigns constantly. We get many of leads a month and couldn’t be happier with their service!” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://trekkingtopnepal.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;trekkingtopnepal.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keyword Research for a Solid Foundation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Competitor Campaign Analysis&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Campaign Creation and Ad Copy Creation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Landing Page Design and Development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Detailed Reporting and Monthly Meeting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;detailed-monthly-ads-reports&quot;&gt;Detailed monthly ads reports&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At MyBetterWeb we manage your Facebook &amp;amp; Google Ads account targeting the keywords that will drive buyers to your site. Highly focused keyword research will determine the most cost-effective approach to obtaining customers who are searching for exactly what you offer. Through the various research tools we use, we will develop effective paid search campaigns focused on meeting your target cost per sale or lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ecommerce-focused-ads-strategies-that-drive-sales&quot;&gt;eCommerce focused ads strategies that drive sales&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By investing in paid ads, you will assist highly eager buyers in finding your site who wouldn’t necessarily find it through organic search engine optimization techniques. Our end goal is to create an campaign with a high ROI (return on investment) that allows your company to spend wisely and grow profitable month after month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-does-adwords-campaign-management-work&quot;&gt;How does AdWords campaign management work?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Paid Campaign Analysis &amp;amp; Implementation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With an established Ads account we will analyze historical data to find what performs most favorably, and tailor other parts to perform in a similar fashion. We will then change bidding options, keywords, ad text, and destination links to align with our goals. The goal is to drive as many leads and/or sales as possible per dollar spent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Conversion Tracking &amp;amp; ROI Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our reports show which keywords are creating leads or sales and which are not. We monitor this to be sure we are focusing on the keywords that are working best and targeting specific phrases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Search Network Advertising&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We monitor progress and engagement of your search network advertising to adjust bigs, ads, and keywords to best reflect the traffic that will engage most positively on your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Ad Variation &amp;amp; Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple ads will be tested using A/B testing methods to determine which ads lead to the highest click-through and conversion rates. We will also develop landing pages, copy variations and test which work best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Monthly Maintenance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All aspects of the account will be reviewed each month to determine what areas can be improved and to be sure the campaign is running smoothly. Negative keywords and changes to your keywords will constantly be made to improve results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:12:12 +0545</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000/#/2018/06/01/paid-search-marketing.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/#/2018/06/01/paid-search-marketing.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
